雷吉娜  你的新专辑《致命冲击》下周发行
Regina, your new album, "Fatal Impact," drops next week.
跟我们说说吧
What can you tell us about it?
这张专辑讲述了爱情  心碎与复仇
It's about love, heartbreak, and revenge.
是我至今最好的专辑
It's my best album yet.
天呐  是乔茜·朗
Oh, my god. It's Josie Lang.
乔茜  看这儿
Josie! Here!
乔茜·朗怎么会来我的发行派对
What the hell is Josie Lang doing at my release party?
她的专辑也下周发行
Her album's out next week, too.
你俩同时出现会吸引更多媒体报道
Having both of you here gets us more press.
报道谁  我还是她
More press for who, me or her?
雷吉娜  谢谢你请我来
Regina. Thank you for the invite.
我是因为你才走上星路
You know, you're the reason I'm a pop star.
我从小学开始就是你的铁杆粉丝
I've been a huge fan ever since I was in grade school.
真是可笑  我怎么就失去选片权了
That is ridiculous. I do not lose a turn.
开玩笑呢  这是规矩啊
Are you kidding? No, that's the rules.
你绝对失去了下次选片权
You absolutely lose your turn.
问他啊  西托
Ask him. 'sito.
怎么了
Ask me what?
一对情侣  选看一部电影
In a relationship, if you choose a movie
但是你选了烂片
and you choose very, very poorly,
你是不是就失去选片权了
do you lose your turn?
有多烂
How poorly?
《情人节》
"Valentine's Day."
-下两次的选片权都失去了  -什么
- You should lose two turns. - What?
-就是这样  -这叫规矩
- Yeah. I'm just saying. - Those are the rules.
-规矩如此嘛  -净瞎说
- Those are the rules. - That's ridiculous.
一个找罐头的流浪汉
So the body was found in this dumpster over here
在垃圾箱里发现了尸体
by a homeless dude who was looking for cans.
尸体用这块油布裹着
It was wrapped up in this tarp.
死因
'cause?
枪伤
G.S.W.
据我观察是近距离开枪
As near as I could tell, she was shot at close range.
流血稀少
Minimal blood seepage
周围没有血液喷溅
and lack of spatter in the area suggests
她是在别处遇害  弃尸在这
she was killed elsewhere, then dumped here.
凶手希望她早上能被垃圾车拖走
So someone was hoping she'd catch a ride with the morning haul,
消失在垃圾场里
disappear under some landfill.
知道身份吗
Any idea who she is?
证件上写着是霍莉·罗兹
Well, according to her I.D., her name is Holly Rhodes.
但她的名片上写着是DJ比特
But her business card has her listed as D.J. Beat.
打电话询问  她的经纪人说
Called the number, and her booking agent says that
她昨晚去苏豪为歌星雷吉娜·凯恩的专辑
she was deejaying an album launch party in SOHO last night
发行派对做DJ
for pop star Regina Cane.
什么
What?
哥们  记得那个MV吗
Aw, dude. You remember that music video
她扮成性感女童军
where she was dressed up as a sexy little girl scout?
不管那饼干有多贵
I don't care what those cookies cost.
我愿卖了左...
I would sell my left...
总之  她到凌晨1点都应该在派对上
Anyway, she was booked at the party till 1:00 a.m.
-1点  -嗯  怎么了
- 1:00 a.m.? - Yeah, why?
我认为死亡时间在晚11点到午夜之间
We're placing the time of death between 11:00 and midnight.
那么她是在派对上遇害的
So whatever happened happened at that party.
这个墨迹像是新的
This ink looks fresh.
号码不在电话薄上
It's an unlisted number.
我给电话公司打电话了
I got a call in to the phone company.
你们在这一带盘查
All right, you guys set up a canvass
看有没有人目击弃尸
for anyone that saw the body dump.
我和卡塞尔去苏豪
Castle and I would head down to SOHO,
问问昨晚的事
see what happened last night.
早啊
Good morning.
好尽兴的派对
Killer party.
看来雷吉娜为推销专辑不遗余力啊
Well, it looks like Regina went all out to promote her new album.
我还记得阿丽克西斯曾经一遍遍地
I remember when Alexis used to play her big hit
播放她的热曲《为爱痴狂》
"Call Me Crazy" over and over again.
我都要发狂了
Drove me crazy.
当然  比不上《情人节》更让人抓狂
Of course, it was no "Valentine's Day."
打扰  纽约警局  主人在哪
Excuse me, NYPD. Where's the host?
别管主人了  你裤子呢
Forget the host. Where's your pants?
是不是
Am I right?
我也经历过  去游泳池边看看
Nah. I've been there. Check by the pool.
你们是纽约什么
Wait. You're N.Y. What now?
警局
P.D.
我是一名警探
As in, a detective.
我们为霍莉·罗兹而来
We're here about Holly Rhodes.
那是谁
Who is Holly Rhodes?
DJ比特
D.J. Beat.
她给你的派对做DJ
She was your deejay for your party.
那个贱人啊
Oh, that skank.
那贱人几乎毁了我的派对
Yeah, bitch almost ruined my entire party.
我为表演做准备时
When I left to get ready for my performance,
她本该保持大家情绪高涨的
she was supposed to stay and get the crowd pumped.
可是她却没影了  音乐也停了
Instead, the music stopped, and she was gone.
她都没回来拿器材
She didn't even come back to get her equipment.
那么说她早走了
So you're saying that she left early?
对
Yeah.
是啊  11点放了个播放列表就走了
Around 11:00, after jacking in a playlist.
我花钱不是让她弄个播放列表了事的
I didn't pay for a playlist.
如果你们看见她  告诉她我要退钱
If you see her, tell her I want my money back.
这个有点困难了
That might be a little tough,
她死了
seeing as she's dead.
她离开你的派对后就死了
She was killed just after leaving your party.
好啊  现在我为抱怨她而不好受了
Great. Now I feel bad for complaining.
你注意到她有异常的行为了吗
Did you notice any unusual behavior?
她跟其他客人起争执了吗
Was she having problems with any of your other guests?
没有  不过我当时忙着招呼大家呢
No. But then again, I was busy making my rounds.
好吧
Right. Okay.
我需要一份宾客名单
Well, I'll need a guest list
以及昨晚所有在这里工作的人的名单
along with the names of everyone that was working last night.
没问题
No problem.
我马上让我的公关发给你们
I'll have my publicist send it right over.
我问过其他几位派对上的宾客
So I spoke with several of the other party guests,
他们都证实了雷吉娜的话
and they confirm Regina's story.
霍莉是突然离场的
Apparently, Holly just suddenly left.
工作中途离场  为什么
In the middle of her set, why?
如果能查明原因  也就知道动机了
Well, we answer that, we'll find out why she was killed.
有人看到她去哪了吗
Anyone see where she went?
没有  没有监控摄像头
No, and there's no security cameras.
我在查对面街的商店有没有可用录像
I'm seeing if I can pull tape from businesses across the street.
你们找到亲属了吗
Did you get ahold of next of kin?
她没有亲人  霍莉是独生女
Nah. She doesn't have any. Holly was an only child.
18岁之前一直在寄养家庭间辗转
Bounced around foster care till she was 18.
这样的童年肯定不幸福
That can't have been an easy childhood.
这也许是她年少时经常
Probably why her hobbies as a teenager
盗窃和偷窃的原因
include burglary and shoplifting.
最终升级到重偷窃罪
Then she graduated to grand theft.
还有近期的案底吗
Anything more recent?
这七年没有了
Not in the last seven years.
她开始专职做DJ之后
She must have cleaned up her act
肯定是金盆洗手了
when she got serious about being a deejay.
还有
Oh, and hey, get this.
在霍莉公寓盘查的警员找到一位邻居
The uniforms canvassing Holly's apartment building found a neighbor
说几天前看到一名男子猛敲霍莉家的门
who saw a man pounding on Holly's door a few days ago.
为什么事
What was it about?
邻居听见他喊"你逃不掉的"
The neighbor heard him scream, "You won't get away with this."
霍莉要么是不在家  要么是有意不应门
Either Holly wasn't home or she wouldn't answer the door,
那人最终还是走了
and eventually, the guy took off.
邻居这会儿正在做描述画像
Neighbor is with a sketch artist as we speak.
好的
Okay.
我查到了霍莉手上那个电话号码
Yo. I got a hit on that phone number written on Holly's hand.
是泰瑞斯·威尔顿的号码
It belongs to a Tyrese Wilton.
是个大牌音乐制作人
Apparently he's some big-time record producer.
他在宾客名单上  他也去了派对
He's on the guest list. He was at the party.
你们去盘问他
You guys see what he knows.
卡塞尔  蕾妮查明被害人被害的地点了
Castle, Lanie knows where our victim was killed.
我剪开她衣服的时候就注意到了
I noticed it when I was cutting her out of her clothes--
她衣服上有污渍
Stains on her outfit.
实验室分析结果是花生油
The lab identified it as peanut oil
含高浓度的谷氨酸钠
with high concentrations of M.S.G.
那么她是吃中餐的时候撒在衣服上了吗
Meaning what, she was eating chinese food and spilled some on herself?
但是  我查了她胃部
Except I checked her stomach contents.
没有中餐
No Chinese.
而且派对上也没有中餐
And they weren't serving any at the party either.
所以我问了鉴证组
So I checked with C.S.U.
他们说垃圾箱上完全没有
They said there was no trace of it in the dumpster,
但是油布上到处是  所以
but it's all over the tarp, meaning...
她可能是在中餐馆或附近被杀
She may have been killed at or near a Chinese restaurant.
那么曼哈顿的大街小巷都有可能了
Narrowing it down to every single block in Manhattan.
枪呢
Uh, what about the gun?
点38的弹头
Slug is from a .380,
但是系统里查不到相符弹道
but there were no ballistic hits in the system.
鉴证组检查油布和衣物的时候
Oh, and when C.S.U. processed the tarp and the clothes,
还找到了这个  人造纤维
they also found these-- synthetic fibers.
也不是垃圾桶里的
They didn't come from the dumpster either.
实验室还在化验中
But the lab is still running tests.
有结果我会通知你
I'll keep you posted.
如果泰瑞斯这么大牌
If Tyrese is so big-time,
为什么他工作室的入口在小巷子里
why is the entrance to his studio in an alley?
因为名人不希望被狗仔队
Because celebrities don't want paparazzi
一天到晚拍照片
taking their picture all the time.
喂  你刚摸了头发吗
Yo, did you just do the hair thing?
什么摸头发
What hair thing?
每次你要去见名人或是美女
Every time you're about to meet a celebrity or a pretty girl,
你就会用手抚弄头发
you run your hand through your hair.
TMZ网站说泰瑞斯
T.M.Z. said that Tyrese
是与乔茜·朗一起参加派对的
was at that party with Josie Lang.
他在制作她的新专辑
He's producing her new album.
她还是比不上雷吉娜
Yeah, well, she's no Regina.
我明白她那女童军的形象
I understand that the image of her as a girl scout
令你刻骨铭心
is seared into your memory,
但乔茜有唱功
But Josie is a real vocalist.
她的粉丝全是12岁小女生
Whose fan base consists of 12-year-old girls...
外加你一个大老爷们
And you.
准备
Stand by.
阿泰  你要我从第二节开始吗
Hey, Ty, you want me to take that from the second bar?
抱歉  小乔  我们停一下
Sorry, Jo. We gotta take 15.
既然乔茜有参加派对
Hey, since Josie was at the party,
我应该去给她录个口供
I should probably take her statement, right?
这里交给你没问题吧  多谢
You got this, right, bro? Thanks.
抱歉  这事太疯狂了
Sorry. This is such a crazy thing.
我不敢相信她死了
I can't believe she's dead.
你跟霍莉有多熟  泰瑞斯
How well did you know Holly, Tyrese?
我在派对上是第一次见到她
I met her for the first time at the party.
我和乔茜一起去的
I was there with Josie
因为我们在合作她的新专辑
'cause we've been working on her album,
而我以前是雷吉娜的制作人
and I used to produce Regina back in the day.
可以告诉我为什么你的电话号码
Can you tell me why we found your phone number
-写在被害人的手上吗  -那个
- written on the victim's hand? - What, that?
我把号码给她  这样我们可以再联络
I gave her my digits so we could set up a meeting.
为了什么事
About what?
要说我拿手的  就是赏识人才
If there's one thing I'm good at, it's spotting talent.
她的混音与节奏感
Her mashups and beat match went better
比大多数现在出专辑的男DJ还要优秀
than most of the guys dropping albums today.
我被她震惊了
I was blown away.
我告诉她我想助她更上一层楼
I told her I wanted to take her to the next level.
那她有什么反应
So how'd she react to that?
非常激动
She was thrilled.
说这样的机会是她一直在争取的
Said a break like this is what she'd been working for.
她应该今天打电话给我的
She was supposed to call me today.
你知不知道她为什么提前离开了派对
You have any idea why she rushed out of that party early?
不知道  可能跟那场争吵有关
Nah. Coulda had something to do with that fight, though.
什么争吵
What fight?
你听说过大恶棍吗
You heard of M.C. Thug?
大恶棍  那个说唱歌手
M.C. Thug? Yeah, the rapper.
-被枪击过七次  对吗  -就是他
- Been shot like seven times, right? - That's the one.
霍莉第一次休息时  他走到了工作台前
Now on Holly's first break, he walked over to her booth,
生气地跟她说了些什么
starts talking to her real low and angry.
我看得出来她生气了
I could see she was getting upset,
想推开他
tried to push him away.
然后他抓住她的手腕说
Then he grabbed her wrist and said,
下次  结果就不是这样了
"Next time, it's gonna end different."
他看到我过去就走了
Then he saw me coming and bounced.
我本来想去问问她情况
Now I was gonna talk to her about it,
但因为和几个朋友讲话耽搁了
but, you know, I got caught up with some folks,
接下来我只知道  她走了
The next thing I knew, she was gone.
霍莉离开后  你在派对上
This M.C. Thug, did you see him at the party anymore
还见过大恶棍吗
after Holly left?
没有  当晚再没见到他
Nah. In fact, I didn't see him the rest of the night.
麻烦你写致珍妮和小凯
So if you can just make it out to Jenny and Kev.
是凯文的简称
It's short for Kevin.
小粉丝  我们走
Hey, fanboy. Let's go.
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
她见到这个会兴奋死的
She's gonna die when she sees this.
谢谢  见到你非常高兴
Thank you. Nice to meet you.
大恶棍
M.C. Thug--
又名达瑞斯·卡森
Aka Darius Carson.
他的前科包括
His rap sheet includes
用致命武器侵犯他人和意图谋杀
assault with a deadly weapon and attempted murder,
这还只是在今年"嘻哈音乐奖"上的"成绩"
and that was just at this year's Hip-Hop Music Awards.
霍莉为什么会被这样的人盯上
How did Holly wind up in the sights of a guy like that?
他们之间的恩怨
Well, whatever was going on between them
是派对以前的事
happened way before that party.
记得猛捶霍莉家门并恐吓她那家伙吗
The guy who was pounding on Holly's door, threatening her?
这是根据邻居的描述画的素描
The sketch just came in from the neighbor.
看起来眼熟吗
Look familiar?
达瑞斯·卡森
Darius Carson--
只有我妈才可以叫我达瑞斯
Nobody calls me Darius unless you my mama,
瞧你那身材  你不是我妈
and by the looks of that body, you ain't.
我肯定你妈妈会为你骄傲的
Yeah, well, I'm sure your mama's so proud.
是啊
Yeah.
达瑞斯
So, Darius,
根据雷吉娜·凯恩的派对策划人所说
according to Regina Cane's party planner,
原来的宾客名单上没有你
you weren't on the original guest list
你是在最后一刻打电话过去
until you made a last-minute phone call
才能够参加派对的
to get in the party.
我喜欢她的音乐  这是犯罪吗
I'm a fan of her music. That a crime?
不  但谋杀是犯罪
No, but murder is.
我知道你不是条子
I know you ain't a cop
高级的衬衫和蓬蓬的头发  唬谁呢
with that fancy shirt and poufy hair.
他不是  但我是
He might not be, but I am.
你确定你去派对是要见雷吉娜吗
Are you sure you went to the party to see Regina?
是  我非常确定
Yeah, I'm real sure.
为什么问
Why?
我们知道你在派对前去过
We know that you visited D.J. Beat's apartment
DJ比特的家
before the party.
我们知道那晚你和她争吵过
We know that you fought with her that night,
然后她被杀害了
and then she turned up dead.
这事跟我可没有关系
I had nothing to do with that mess.
但你跟她之间有过节
Yeah, but you had something to do with her.
说对了  我要拿回我女人的手链
Damn straight. I wanted my girl's bracelet back.
谁拿了你女人的手链
Who had your girl's bracelet?
上周我在家办了场派对
I threw a party at my crib last week.
我请了DJ比特去助兴
I hired D.J. Beat to spipin.
第二天  我女人达科塔
The next day, my girl Dakota
发现她的钻石手链不见了
realized her diamond bracelet is missing.
那个贱人和她的贱人助手
Now that bitch and her little bitch of an assistant
是唯一我不能打包票的人
are the only ones there I couldn't vouch for.
贱人还有贱人助手吗
The bitch had an assistant bitch?
对  那个小混蛋为她工作
Yeah, the little punk that works for her.
所以你跟踪她到派对
So then you tracked her down to the party.
她离开后  你跟上并杀害了她
And when she ran, you followed her and you killed her.
没有  我给她一天时间把手链物归原主
No, I told her she had a day to cough it up
否则的话
or else.
否则的话会怎样
Or else what?
说"否则的话"一般就够了
"Or else" is usually enough.
晚上11点到12点你在哪里
Where were you between 11:00 and midnight?
楼上  和我女人一起
Upstairs... with my girl.
达科塔吗
Dakota?
不同的女人  凯娅
Different girl. Kaiya.
调查清楚前你得待在这里
All right. Well, I'm gonna have to hold you while we look into that.
很好  这对我在道上的名号有帮助
Good. That helps my street cred.
你们会为我拍疑犯照片  对吗
You guys are gonna do a mug shot, right?
我带了我自己的灯光师过来
'cause I brought my lighting guy with me.
谢谢
Thanks.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
凯娅确认她和大恶棍在一间卧室
So Kaiya confirms that she was "Hanging out" with M.C. Thug
一起"玩"到12点半
in one of the bedrooms till 12:30.
他的确有报警说丢了钻石手链
And he did file a police report about the missing bracelet.
所以我调了一份去年
So I requested a list of all the parties
霍莉工作的所有派对的记录
that Holly worked in the past year.
超过50场派对
Of the more than 50 events,
有七宗失窃案
turns out that thefts were reported in seven of them.
作案手法全一样  大多数是偷高档珠宝
M.O. is the same every time-- mostly high-end jewelry.
总价值差不多有五十万
In total, almost half a million bucks.
都是在高档住宅区办的派对上偷的
All taken from parties at upscale residences.
我从霍莉的经纪人那里得知
And I also confirmed with Holly's booking agent
她工作时有个助理
that she always worked with an assistant--
保罗·特维斯
Paul Travers.
也就是说他们俩是一伙的
Okay, so the two of them are a crew
借着她的手艺  进入高档住宅
using her deejay skills to access high-end homes
顺手牵羊
and then cleaning them out along the way.
她以前确实有过盗窃史
She does have a history of theft,
没准是重操旧业了
so maybe she went back to her old ways.
如果那个助理和她一起参加了派对的话
But if the assistant worked the party with her,
他现在在哪呢  怎么不见踪影了
then where is he and why hasn't he come forward?
只有一个原因  他被牵涉其中
There's only one reason. He was involved.
牵涉什么
I-involved in what?
我的朋友去世了  你们的意思是
My friend is dead, and now you're saying, what,
我们是"邦妮和克莱德"吗[雌雄大盗]
like, we're like Bonnie and Clyde?
保罗  你们俩参加的七个派对
Paul, thefts were reported at seven of the parties
都有盗窃案发生
that you both worked.
因为她有案底  就一定是她干的吗
Oh, and so because of her history, it's gotta be her?
音乐拯救了她  她已经改过自新了
Music saved her. She was done with that life.
那你呢
And what about you?
据霍莉的经纪人所说
According to Holly's agency,
你负责安装和拆卸器具
you were responsible for setting up and breaking down the equipment.
-然后呢  -你昨晚没有把器具归位
- So? - So you never broke it down last night.
你中途离开了派对  一去不回
You left the party, never came back,
霍莉也一样
same as Holly.
区别是你现在还活着  她却归了西
Only you're still alive, and she's dead.
-昨晚吗  -对
- Last night? - Mm-hmm.
我昨晚压根没去
I wasn't even there last night.
保罗  别说谎
Paul, don't lie.
她的单子上有你的名字
She's got you listed on her invoice.
我知道
Yeah, I... I-I know.
近一年来她好几次都是临时打给我
A few times this past year, she'd call me up last minute
说要换人
to say she was using another guy.
通常是说她的表亲之类的需要这份工作
It was, like, her cousin or something, and he needed the work.
我知道她挺愧疚的
I-I know she felt bad about it
因为她还是照付了我的工钱
'cause she still offered to pay me anyway.
昨天晚上我去参加生日晚餐了
I-I was at a birthday dinner last night.
我有证人
I have witnesses.
这些派对里
Which of these parties
有哪些你没参加
did the other guy work?
这个
This one.
这个  这个
This one. Here.
This one. This one.
这个  和那个
This one, and that one.
正好是有盗窃案发生的派对
The same ones that reported robberies.
目前只有一个目击证人  一个服务员
So far only one witness, a caterer,
记得昨晚有人安装了霍莉的设备
remembers seeing a guy setting up Holly's equipment last night.
她是从背面看到的
And she only saw him from behind,
他当时穿着帽衫
and he was wearing a hoodie.
我们在询问其他派对嘉宾
So we've reached out to other party guests
看有没有人能描述得详细一点
to see if we can get a better description.
昨晚有东西被窃吗
So was anything stolen from the party last night?
没有  我们问过所有人了
No. We asked everyone.
到现在为止没有任何物品失踪报告
And so far, no one's reported anything missing.
警员又搜查了霍莉的公寓
So UNIs searched Holly's apartment again.
没找到被窃物品
There's no sign of the stolen goods,
她的账号也没有大笔资金流入
and there's no influx of cash into her account,
所以就算她在以此挣钱
so if she was making money off this thing,
也没有相关证据
there's no evidence of it.
会不会是
What if this
这个神秘的助理掌控了一切
mystery assistant is the one behind it all?
想想看吧
I mean, think about it.
他强迫霍莉带他进入这些派对
He forces Holly to get him into these parties.
她忙着工作的时候
While she's busy spinning,
他就可以随心所欲地在豪宅里走动
he's free to walk around these fancy apartments.
而他是工作人员
And since he's hired help,
没人会留意他
nobody pays him any attention.
真是易如反掌
It's candy from a baby.
但当大恶棍质问霍莉时  她害怕了
But when M.C. Thug confronted Holly, she got scared.
所以她决定告发那个助理
So she threatened to blow the whistle on the assistant.
这确实可以成为谋杀动机
Well, that would certainly give him motive for murder.
但单子上是保罗的名字
But with Paul's name on the invoice,
没有他的记录  要怎样才能找到他呢
there's no record of him. How are we gonna find him?
昨晚是他安装了那些器具  对吧
He helped set up that equipment last night, right?
那上面应该有他的指纹
His fingerprints would be on it.
叫鉴证组去查
Get C.S.U. on it.
好繁重的工作啊  我一会儿再来
Grunt work. I'll come back later.
-你留下咖啡就行  -有何发现
- So long as you leave the coffee. - What did you find?
霍莉的通话记录
Holly's phone records.
她总会在有盗窃案发生的派对当天
She received calls from a pay phone in Washington Heights
接到来自华盛顿高地
the same days that she was booked
一处付费电话的来电
for the parties where the thefts happened.
也许是她的神秘助理打来询问细节的
Well, maybe it's her mystery assistant, calling for details.
霍莉就是在华盛顿高地长大的
Holly grew up in the heights,
所以有可能是老邻居
so it might be someone from the old neighborhood,
但我们还是找不到他
but it doesn't bring us any closer to finding him.
没必要费心了
Doesn't need to.
鉴证组在器材上取到一副指纹
C.S.U. matched a print on that equipment
和一个叫做乔伊·马龙的人相符  代号"怪兽"
to one Joey Malone-- street name, "Monster."
他的前科累累
He's got a list of priors a mile long.
警员在华盛顿高地抓到了他
UNIs took him down in Washington Heights.
已经押回来了  去看看吧
He's in the box. Come take a look.
怪兽
Monster?
这名字听起来像是帮派团伙
Now that sounds like the kind of ganged-up thug
能一枪要你命
that would shoot you dead
然后把你丢在某个垃圾堆的那种
and leave you in a dumpster someplace.
一半血肉之躯  一半壮如高山
Probably half man, half mountain,
全身都是监狱纹身
full of prison tats.
或者  是那种沉默的危险分子
Or is he quietly dangerous?
有着贾维尔·巴登
You know, like, Javier Bardem
在影片中的那种奇怪发型
in any movie where he's got weird hair.
你自己一睹芳容吧
Just take a look for yourself.
这位就是
Behold...
怪兽
Monster.
更像饼干怪兽
More like cookie monster.
我们对这小子有什么了解
So what do we know about this kid?
首先他不是霍莉的亲戚
Well, he's not related to Holly, for one.
他的父亲在他七岁时死于吸毒过量
His father died of a drug overdose when he was 7.
母亲在几年前自杀身亡
His mom committed suicide a couple of years ago.
他的叔叔马丁·戴克
His uncle--Martin Decker--
后来成为了他的监护人
is the one who took over guardianship.
他的叔叔现在在哪
Where's his uncle now?
他不在家  我联系了社会服务
He's not at home. I notified social services,
他们或许知道怎样联系到他
thinking they might know how to reach him.
你说他有前科
You said that he had priors.
对  他曾因非法侵入
Yeah, he was busted for breaking and entering,
盗窃罪和拒捕而被捕
burglary, resisting arrest.
现在他升级到谋杀了
Now he's moved up to the big leagues.
现在怎么办
So, uh, what's the plan here?
我一个人进去  省得他觉得咱们以多欺少
I'm gonna go in alone so he doesn't feel outnumbered,
看他怎么说
see what he's made out of.
他才14岁
He's 14.
难以相信他能做这些事
It's hard to believe he's capable of something like this.
在他的世界就不奇怪了
Not in his world, it isn't.
乔伊
Hi, Joey.
我是凯特·贝克特探长
I'm Detective Kate Beckett.
你可真是个辣妹
A major Hottie is what you are.
好了  不说废话
Okay. Now that we got that cleared up,
你得回答我几个问题
I need to ask you a few questions.
你得先征得我监护人的允许
You need permission from my guardian.
据我回忆  我还未成年
The last time I checked, I'm a minor.
我们正在努力联系你叔叔
Well, we're making our best effort to get ahold of your uncle.
但同时  纽约警局的规定允许我和你谈话
In the meantime, NYPD policy allows me to talk to you.
那就说吧
Well, so talk.
我们在查霍莉·罗兹被害一案
We're looking into the murder of Holly Rhodes.
我听说这事了
Heard about that.
我很难过
Real sad.
我知道两天前  你还给她打过工
I understand that two nights ago, you worked for her.
你当时看见她和谁起过分歧没
Did you see her having problems with anyone?
没
No.
你知道她为什么提前离开派对吗
Do you know why she left the party early?
不知道
Nope.
-你知道她去哪了吗  -不晓得
- Do you know where she went? - No clue.
那我这么问你吧
Okay, let me ask you this--
你觉得霍莉为什么会雇个有前科的
Why did you think Holly hired a 14-year-old kid
14岁小毛孩做她的技术助理
With a record to be her tech assistant?
因为我最棒啊
'cause I'm the best.
做什么最棒  偷东西吗
The best at what, stealing?
每次你帮霍莉做事
Every time you've worked for Holly,
都有高档珠宝遗失
High-end jewelry has gone missing--
每次都是
Every single time.
我不知道啊
I don't know nothin' about that.
霍莉知道你偷东西吗
Did Holly know about the stealing
或是当晚她发现了
or did she find out that night?
所以你就杀了她
Is that why you killed her?
什么  什么  杀她
What--what? Kill her?
不不
No. No.
我没有杀她
I didn't do that.
有目击者称见到你
We have witnesses that saw you
在她离开派对后马上就走了
leave the party right after she did.
你也没有再回来拿设备器材
And you never came back for the equipment.
那么在11点到午夜这段时间你在哪
So where were you between 11:00 and midnight?
我在  我在"电视国王"
I was at-- I was at TV king.
你离开派对
You left the party
不拿设备  去了"电视国王"
and the equipment to go to TV King
还是在半夜
in the middle of the night?
你应该想个更好的说辞  乔伊
You're gonna have to do better than that, Joey.
他们允许你来盘问我
You may be allowed to talk to me...
但我不一定要回答
But I don't have to talk back.
盗窃加谋杀
Robbery and murder?
或许野兽这绰号还不赖
Maybe monster wasn't such a bad nickname after all.
我还不能确定
You know what? I'm not sure about that.
他预料这场对话是关于盗窃的
He expected the conversation about the stealing,
但当我指控他谋杀霍莉的时候
but when I accused him of murdering Holly,
他懵了
That threw him.
我知道原因了  乔伊的不在场证明成立了
And I think I know why. Joey's alibi checks out.
真的吗  他在"电视国王"
Seriously, he was at TV King?
副经理有时让他
The assistant manager sometimes lets him
在大屏幕上打游戏
play video games up on the big screen,
霍莉的死亡时间区内  乔伊一直在那里
and that's where Joey was during Holly's time of death.
如果他没有杀霍莉  那会是谁呢
Well, then if he didn't kill Holly, then who did?
操控这一切的人  就是凶手
The brains behind this operation, that's who.
像乔伊这样砸橱窗抢劫的孩子
A kid like Joey goes from smash-and-grabs
转而偷50万的珠宝
to stealing a half a mil in jewelry?
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
有人在背后教唆
Someone put him up to this.
对  这说得通  有时精明的罪犯
No, that makes sense. Sometimes savvy criminals
叫小喽啰去做不法的事
use minors to do their dirty work.
当然
Of course.
就像《雾都孤儿》里的费金
A Fagin to Joey's Oliver Twist.
如果再加上霍莉  她就是机灵鬼神偷
And if Holly's involved, that makes her the artful dodger,
或者狡猾DJ
or the artful deejay.
推理得不错嘛
Ooh, nicely played.
这就解释了我们在霍莉或乔伊家
And that would explain why we never found
找不到赃物的原因
the stolen loot in Holly or Joey's apartments.
费金拿去了
Fagin has it.
他有动机除掉霍莉
That gives him motive to get rid of Holly
如果她找他麻烦的话
if she ever gave him any trouble.
如果我们猜对了
Well, if we're right,
那么乔伊肯定知道谁是凶手
then Joey knows who our killer is.
我来搞定这孩子
I get this kid.
我去跟他聊聊
Let me get a crack at him.
那位超辣警探去哪了
Hey, where's the super-hot detective?
不就是我吗  别笑
Oh, you're looking at him. Don't laugh.
我可上过纽约警局日历
I was featured in the NYPD calendar.
肯定卖得"很好"
I bet that was a big seller.
那么
So, uh,
你肯定是来扮好警察的
you must be the good cop.
这我就不知道了
Well, I don't know about that.
但我可以保你出去
But I could be your ticket out of this.
是吗
Yeah? Mm-hmm.
怎么保
How's that work?
我们知道你没有杀霍莉
We know you didn't kill Holly.
你只是顺了一堆珠宝回去
All you did was lift a bunch of jewelry.
省省吧
Nah, nah, just save it.
我们不管珠宝的事
We don't care about the jewelry.
我们可以把指控全部撤销
We can take those charges off the table.
我们要的就是那个指使你的人的名字
All we want is the guy who put you up to it.
我都不知道你在说些什么
I don't even know who you're talking about.
乔伊  行了
Joey, come...
我刚给了你一张中了奖的彩票
I just gave you the winning lottery ticket.
你现在应该做的
Now the right move here
是兑现彩票  而不是撕了它
is to cash that in, not tear it up.
我猜你接着要对我说
I bet this is the part where you tell me,
我不了解自己的处境多么严重
I don't know the seriousness of my situation.
除非我把知道的都告诉你
How unless I tell you everything I know,
不然你帮不了我
You can't help me.
然后你倾身向我  显得很关心我
And then you'll lean in close, like you care about me
好像是我朋友一样
and like you're my friend,
然后许下永远不会兑现的承诺
and you'll make promises you'll never keep.
我说话算话  兄弟
I keep all my promises, bro.
人人都那么说
That's what everybody says.
这个条件是有时限的  乔伊
This is a limited-time offer, Joey.
不感兴趣
Not interested.
好吧
Okay.
看看这个
I want you to take a look at this.
这就是霍莉最后的样子
This is how Holly ended up--
被枪杀
Shot,
被抛尸于垃圾场
tossed in the garbage.
你觉得她该遭受这些吗
Now you think she deserved that, hmm?
怎么了
Oh, wh-what?
怎么不再自作聪明了呢
No smart-ass comeback now, huh?
你跟这个女人一起工作
You worked with this woman.
你了解她
You knew her.
同一个人
The same guy
教唆你和霍莉去偷珠宝
who has you stealing jewelry did this to Holly.
他利用你们这样的孩子
He uses kids like you.
却逍遥法外
And then he just gets to walk away
而你却要坐在这里回答我的问题
while you have to sit in here and answer all my questions.
你知道你现在对他来说是什么吗
You know what you are to him right now?
用剩的废物
You're a loose end.
好好看看这些
So take a hard look,
因为你也是这个下场
because this is your future.
这就是你
This is you.
你错了
You're wrong.
他不会伤害我
He won't hurt me.
他是不会  前提是我们能阻止他
He won't. Not once we stop him.
我只要知道他的名字  乔伊
All I need is his name, Joey.
我还是不知道你在说些什么
I still don't know who you're talking about.
乔伊父母死后我一直是他的社工
I've been Joey's caseworker since his parents died.
不用说  这差事不顺利
Needless to say, it hasn't been smooth sailing,
但我想象不出他会做这种事
but I can't imagine he'd do anything like this.
我们觉得策划盗窃的另有其人
Well, we think that the thefts were someone else's idea.
你知道谁会
Do you know of anyone in his life
让他做这些事吗
who might have drawn him into this?
不知道  如果说有这么个人我也不吃惊
No, but it wouldn't surprise me if there was someone.
他的叔叔显然不是个好榜样
His uncle's not exactly a strong role model.
他叔叔怎么样  他现在在哪
What about his uncle? Where is he now?
我们正在找他
We're trying to track him down.
他可能在俱乐部  他是扑克玩家
He may be in A.C. He's a card player.
这家伙听着真混蛋
Guy sounds like a real prize.
你想给这些孩子最好的选择
You want the best option for these kids.
但有时你手里却是最差的选择
And sometimes all you have is the least-bad option.
让我想到乔伊的这桩事
Which brings me to the issue of what to do with Joey.
你们要指控他盗窃吗
Are you charging him with theft?
希望不会
We were hoping not to.
那我要把他送去临时寄养
So... I'll put him in temporary foster care.
等等  现在他在那不安全
Whoa, whoa, whoa. He's not safe out there in the world right now.
我们在找的人杀了一名女子
The guy that we're after killed a woman.
他会对乔伊做出同样的事
He could do the same thing to Joey.
那你可以让他进少教所
Then you can put him in protective custody
进行保护性监禁
in juvenile hall.
我不能把他丢到少管所
I-I can't just throw him in juvie.
我在争取他的信任
I'm trying to gain his trust here.
库珀女士  这小孩是破这宗谋杀案的关键
Ms. Cooper, this boy is the key to us solving a murder.
很抱歉  可这由不得你
Well, I'm sorry, but those are the choices.
如果我带他走呢
What if I take him?
那样的话  他既不用被关起来
That way, he's not locked up,
我又能保证他的安全
and I can keep him safe.
我还能继续做他的工作
And I can continue to work on him.
怎么样
What about that?
我...
I...
我想我可以延后他的报告
I suppose I could delay his paperwork,
但只许这一晚
but this would be for one night,
这表示乔伊·马龙由你负责
and it means that Joey Malone is your responsibility.
可以  交给我了
It's cool. I got this.
这孩子没有爸爸
The kid doesn't have a father.
他可能正需要有人沟通
He probably just needs someone to connect with.
我宁可和那个女警办睡衣派对
I'd rather have a pajama party with the lady cop.
是吗  我倒觉得是我倒霉
Yeah? Well, it looks like I drew the short straw, literally.
伙计  难怪你单身
Man, no wonder you're single.
没女人愿意待在这里
No woman would spend time here
除非是被强迫的
unless it was against her will.
你呢  玛莎·斯图尔特
Yeah, what about you, Martha Stewart?
你家该是什么样
What's your place supposed to be,
破旧时尚风吗  重点号加在破旧上
shabby chic, emphasis on shabby?
是不入流  但不是我的错
It's a dive, but it's not my fault.
我叔叔宁可把钱都输在赌桌上
My uncle would rather blow all of his money at the tables.
那一定是他忙得没空给我们回电的原因了
Must be why he's too busy to call us back.
别等电话了
Don't wait by the phone.
他抚养我就是为了拿点钱
He only cares about claiming me as a dependent.
我父母在我五岁时就离异了
My parents split up when I was 5.
伙计  别把腿放在我的桌上
Man, get your feet off my table.
老爸和新任妻子搬去了福罗里达
Dad moved to Florida with his new wife.
之后就是电话或是明信片联系
Most I ever got after that was a phone call or a postcard.
-明信片  -对
- Postcard? - Yeah.
你几岁了
How old are you, anyway?
很老了  可...
Ancient, but...
我那时还太小  印象不深了
I'm young enough to remember what it was like.
你一定想念你的家人
You must miss your folks.
我爸死后  我妈继续生活
After my dad died, my mom kept going.
她试着假装
You know, she tried to pretend
我们还是完整家庭
that we were still a normal family.
她尽力对我关怀备至
She did her best to take care of me
直到
until...
她也无能无力
she couldn't do it anymore.
现在你自己照顾自己
Now you take care of yourself.
对
Yeah.
听着  伙计  我知道你没必要这么做
Look, man, I know you didn't have to do this.
我是说收留我
Take me in, I mean.
所以  谢了
So, uh, thanks.
我去给你拿条毯子
I'm gonna go grab you a blanket,
还有枕头
pillow.
至少你买了很多"AV"产品
At least you didn't skimp out on the audio-visual budget.
没错
You know that's right.
对了  我还有《刺客信条3》
Oh, and I got "Assassin's Creed III."
把这当做自己家吧
So go ahead and knock yourself out.
对了  设定双人游戏模式
Oh, and, uh, put it on dual-player mode
我能回去教教你
so I can come back and school you.
是啊  我赌二十块
Yeah, 20 bucks says
你过不了第一关
you won't make it past level one.
什么  说瞎话呢
What? Crazy.
坐下
Sit down.
好吧
Okay.
可以解释一下吗
Care to explain?
什么  这副手铐
What, the handcuffs?
不不  你脚上穿的那双时髦的鞋
No, no. The stylish shoes that you're wearing.
当然是手铐了
Yes, the handcuffs.
臭小子昨晚想学胡迪尼开溜
Well, junior here tried to pull a Houdini on me last night.
胡迪尼[逃脱魔术大师]是谁
Who the hell is houdini?
-闭嘴  -从窗口逃出去的
- Shut up. - Out the window?
对
Yeah.
从逃生梯下去的
Down the fire escape?
对  然后跳上了一辆正在行驶的垃圾车
Yeah, and then on to a moving garbage truck.
然后用滑板滑行了五条街
Then on a skateboard for 5 blocks,
一直到了"L"轻轨
which took him all the way to the "L" train.
你怎么追上的
How'd you keep up?
-没追上  -闭嘴  搞什...  给我
- He didn't. - Shut up. What the... give me that.
我征用了一个人的自行车
I commandeered this dude's bicycle,
然后我在地铁把他跟丢了
and then he lost me in the subway.
可后来我在下一站抓住了他
But then I caught him at the next stop.
他很狡猾
Kid's wily.
可姜还是老的辣
But I'm wilier.
活脱脱的《法国贩毒网》
Wow. Just like "The French Connection."
与此同时  用来裹霍莉尸体的油布
In the meantime, C.S.U. was able to I.D. those fibers
鉴证组已经能确认上面的纤维了
found on the tarp that Holly's body was wrapped in.
-哪里来的  -德国
- Where are they from? - Germany.
据化学成分和颜色判断
Based on the chemical composition and color,
是地毯纤维
they're fibers from carpeting
被高端欧洲汽车制造商
used by a high-end European car manufacturer
用来填车后行李箱的
to line their vehicles' trunks.
我们现在知道霍莉的尸体
Well, now we know how Holly's body
最后出现在建筑工地
ended up at that construction site.
鉴证组已经把范围缩小到2010到2012款X5型号
C.S.U. narrowed it down to a model 2010 to 2012 X5.
我会排查建筑工地附近
I'll canvass around the construction site,
看看有没有人看到那种车
see if anyone saw a car like that
在垃圾车附近出现
hanging around the dumpster.
我们从中心办事处拿到了乔伊的少年犯记录
So we pulled Joey's juvie files from the central clerk's office.
理论上  任何跟他有瓜葛的人
Theory being, whoever he's involved with
都记录在这上面
might be in there somewhere.
除非他把名字告诉你
Unless he gave you a name.
没
Uh, n-no.
还没
Not exactly.
我们找到和乔伊打交道的人
Look, we find out who Joey got mixed up with,
就能找到凶手
we find our killer.
这些档案里会有线索直指凶手
There's gotta be something in these files that points to him.
他在11岁时
Looks like he got his first taste
就尝到了非法闯入的滋味了
with a B&E when he was 11 years old.
12岁时升级到了盗窃
Graduated to burglary when he was 12--
和一个身份不明的成年男性
Broke in to a mom-and-pop corner store
破门进入一家家庭经营的街头小店
along with an identified adult male.
或许他就是我们要找的人
Maybe he's the one we're looking for.
不  我们要找的不是这种被抓的笨蛋
No, we're not looking for someone who he was busted with.
这家伙够机灵  一直躲在幕后
This guy's smart enough to stay above it all.
看这里
Check this out.
两个月前  一个叫肖恩·温特斯的人
Two months ago, someone named Shane Winters
在他被控入店行窃后
bailed him out after he was picked up
保释他出来
on a shoplifting charge.
肖恩·温特斯  我记得这个名字
Shane Winters? I remember that name.
死者霍莉·罗兹17岁时
When Holly Rhodes, our victim, was 17,
她因重偷窃罪被捕
she was busted on a grand theft charge.
看看是谁签的保释单
And check out who posted bail.
肖恩·温特斯
Shane Winters.
就是他了
That's our guy.
肖恩·温特斯
Shane Winters.
贩毒  重盗窃罪
Trafficking, grand theft,
致命武器攻击罪  敲诈勒索
assault with a deadly weapon, extortion--
这家伙无所不干
This dude has dabbled in everything.
在霍莉还是问题少女时
So when Holly was a troubled teen,
一定在为肖恩效命  就跟乔伊一样
she must have worked for Shane, just like Joey is.
可后来她洗手不干  脱离这样的生活
But then she cleaned herself up, got out of the life.
后来肖恩发现
Then when Shane figured out
她能进入各大高端派对
what kind of access she had at the parties,
就把她拉了回来
he pulled her back in.
这也解释了霍莉
Well, that explains why Holly
为何会雇佣乔伊做助手
had to hire Joey as an assistant.
刚查了肖恩·温特斯  猜猜他的座驾是什么
Just ran Shane Winters. Guess what he drives.
2010款X5
2010 X5.
也许里面有在油布上发现的纤维
That would have the carpet fibers we found on the tarp.
是啊  一个任你装尸体的后备箱
Yeah, and a roomy trunk for all your body-moving needs.
-我们得把他带进来问话  -试过了
- We gotta bring him in. - We tried to.
警员去了他最后登记的住址  人不在
UNIs busted in on his last-known address. He's not there.
你这算什么  保姆警官吗
So what are you, officer babysitter?
能加工资吗
Do you get paid extra for doing that?
肖恩·温特斯在哪儿
Where's Shane Winters?
我的苏打水在哪儿
Where's my soda?
LT没事儿
L.T.
你以为对他来说你很特别  是吗
You figure you're special to him, don't you?
你并不是
Well, you're not.
老兄
Man...
你还是不懂
You don't get it.
我不会出卖他的
I'm not giving him up.
你一直不松口
You know how much time keeping your mouth shut
用不了多久
is gonna buy you with Shane
肖恩就会掏枪毙了你
as long as it takes him to pull his gun and shoot you with it.
然后他会再找另一个像你一样的孩子
And then he's just gonna move on to the next lost kid.
别让事情变成这样  乔伊
Don't let it end that way, Joey.
告诉我他在哪儿
Just tell me where I can find him.
我不是叛徒
I'm not a rat.
有收获吗
Any luck?
我真想拧断这小混蛋的脖子
Man, I just want to wring this little bastard's neck right now.
我想是没收获
I'm gonna call that a no.
我们对肖恩的车发布通缉了
So we got a BOLO out on Shane and his car.
小孩真恐怖啊  老兄
Freakin' kids, man.
真不知道你怎么挺过来的
I don't know how you do it, bro.
不不  闺女那么乖是我撞大运了
Oh, no, no. I lucked out with Alexis.
有时候  你会觉得
At a certain point, you realize you're just...
我们只是在和生活经验没有我们丰富的人打交道
dealing with someone who hasn't been around as long as we have.
他们要找到自己的路
They have to find their way.
问题是  他已经找到自己的路了
The problem is, he's already found his way.
他只是没看到后果
He just doesn't see where it's gonna put him.
还没发现肖恩的车
Hey, no luck on the BOLO.
但我和盗窃部的加西亚谈过
But I talked to Garcia in robbery.
知道肖恩在哪儿了
We got a tip on Shane's location.
你要去吗
You want to roll?
这次让我来
You know what? Let me get this one.
嗨  帅哥
Hey, sugar.
想喝点啥
What's your poison?
大侠
Hello.
想喝点啥
What are you drinking?
温特斯先生今天不见客
Mr. Winters is not taking any meetings today.
能给我拿一袋冰块吗
Can I just get a bag of ice, please?
你要冰块干什么
What the hell do you want with a bag of ice?
给他用
It's for him.
借过
Excuse me.
你一定是埃斯波西托警探了
You must be Detective Esposito.
乔伊告诉我你俩在"约会"呢
Joey told me you two been hanging out.
他说早晚你得找到我这儿来
Said sooner or later, you'd find your way down here.
他警告你了
So he warned you.
他是个好孩子  很可靠
Yeah, he's a good kid. Dependable.
戴上
Put 'em on.
不戴更好  算你拒捕
Or better yet, resist arrest.
求你别带了
Please.
改天吧再玩吧
Some other time, maybe. Huh?
你认识一个叫霍莉·罗兹的女人吗  肖恩
Do you know a woman named Holly Rhodes, Shane?
-耳熟  -当然
- Name sounds familiar. - Well, it should.
多年前她跟你混过
You ran with her back in the day.
她是混过  但不是和我一起
Oh, she ran, but not with me.
那她十几岁的时候你为什么保她出来
Then why did you bail her out when she was a teenager?
我就是喜欢小孩儿
Well, I got a soft spot for kids, man.
是哦
Yeah, yeah.
你就像老好先生
You're just like a regular Mr. Rogers.
你最后一次见她是什么时候  肖恩
When was the last time you saw her, Shane?
最后一次见霍莉吗
Uh, last time I saw Holly?
想不起来了
Don't recall.
让我帮你想想
Well, let me help you out with that.
三天之前
It's three nights ago...
你杀她的时候
when you killed her.
这你可说错了
You're wrong about that.
我们没说错
Mm. I don't think so.
霍莉接的那些DJ演出
See, when this whole deejaying gig of Holly's took off--
大把的有钱客户和高级公寓
wealthy clients, penthouses--
你看到了一个金灿灿的致富机会
you saw a golden, diamond-encrusted opportunity.
于是你就说服霍莉
And that's when you pressured Holly
带乔伊·马龙在身边  充当助手
into bringing in Joey Malone as an assistant.
他在这些派对上游荡
He'd go in to these fancy parties,
拿着价值五十万美元的高档首饰
and he'd walk right out the front door
大摇大摆地从大门走出去
with a half a million in high-end jewelry,
看起来和你毫无关系
And your hands would stay clean.
最后一句说得对
Well, you are right about that part at least.
的确和我没关系
My hands are clean.
但是最近一次派对却出了岔子
But then something went wrong at this last party.
也许霍莉不想干了
I mean, maybe Holly pushed back.
或者她想让你从她生活里永远消失
Or maybe she wanted you out of her life, once and for all.
但她知道的太多
But she knew too much
她才应该消失
so she had to go.
我听到的都是
Look, all I hear you guys saying
你们毫无根据的废话
is a whole lot of stuff that you can't prove.
我们能证明她的尸体曾经在你的车里
Well, we can prove that her body was in your trunk.
粘在卷霍莉尸体的布料上的纤维
Fibers stuck to the tarp that Holly was wrapped in
和你宝马X5里的纤维相匹配
match your X5.
我们要扣押你的车
We're impounding it right now.
我想你们可能没听说
Wow. Then I guess you guys didn't hear about it--
今天早上我的车出了点小问题
about the little problem I had with my vehicle this morning.
我太不小心了
You see, I got a little careless.
本来我在点烟
I was, uh, I was lighting a cigarette,
结果整个车就着火了
and next thing I know, whole car catches on fire.
里面外面  还有地毯  整个烧得跟薯片似的
Inside, outside, the carpet-- whole thing burned to a crisp.
我不想扫你们的兴
I hate to tell you,
不过恐怕已经没有纤维给你们对比了
but there's probably not a fiber left to match.
太巧了  不是吗
Crazy how things happen sometimes, huh?
再说一遍
So, again,
你们说的都是毫无根据的废话
whole lot of noise that you can't prove.
到这里吧
That being said,
我要找我的律师
I'd like my lawyer.
你先出去一下
I need a minute alone.
你给肖恩通风报信了
You tipped off Shane.
昨晚跑了之后
After you bolted last night,
你给他打了电话
you called him.
警告他已经成为了嫌疑人
Warned him that he was a suspect,
好让他有机会烧车
which gave him a chance to torch his car.
掩盖他弃尸的罪证
Cover up his role in Holly's death.
恭喜你啊  乔伊
Congratulations, Joey.
你帮他逃脱了谋杀的指控
You helped him get away with murder.
如果有用的话
Now I'd beat your skinny little ass
我真想扒了你的裤子打你一顿
for being so stupid if it'd change anything.
我想也没用  因为
But it won't because, well...
你太忠诚了
You're so loyal.
看看肖恩是怎么报答你的
Now let's see how Shane returns the favor.
我看出来了  你反应有点迟钝
Look, I can see that you're a little slow,
但我刚刚说了"我要找我的律师"
but I just said, "I want my lawyer."
我想跟你谈那些盗窃案
This is about the thefts.
总得有人当替罪羊
Somebody's gonna have to go down for 'em,
我们也都知道那人会是乔伊·马龙
and we know it's gonna be Joey Malone.
地检官想把他当做成年人来起诉
The D.A. wants to try him as an adult.
那肯定会蹲上好几年
That means hard time.
你还是爷们一点
All you gotta do is man up.
承担下来
Man up about the thefts,
我就可以去地检官那求情
and then maybe I can talk to the D.A.
让他给乔伊减刑
And get Joey a deal.
听着  老兄
Look, man,
犯了罪  坐牢是应该的
If the kid did the crime, he's gotta do the time.
还要看吗
Have you seen enough?
你还想护着他吗
You still want to protect him?
我交代
Look...
就像你说的
It was like you said.
我通常跟着霍莉混进去
I'd go in with Holly,
顺走一些昂贵的珠宝
Lift pricey jewelry,
顺的越多越好
The more the better.
但是这次  有些不一样
But this time, it was different.
怎么不一样
Why?
肖恩告诉我目标是个音乐制作人
Shane told me my mark was this music producer,
-泰瑞斯  -泰瑞斯·威尔顿
- Tyrese--  -Tyrese Wilton?
对  就是他  不过很奇怪
Yeah, him. It was weird.
我的任务是去偷他的手机
I was supposed to boost his cell phone.
为什么要偷他的手机
Why his cell phone?
不知道  但我还是偷了
I don't know, but I took it.
好吧  然后呢
Yeah, and then what?
不知怎么被霍莉发现了  她很生气
Somehow Holly found out, and she flipped.
她找到我让我把手机还回去
She got in my face and told me to give the phone back.
我有些害怕  因为我知道她一生气惹不起
And I got scared because I knew she carried heat,
但是我已经把手机交给肖恩
but I had already handed the phone off to Shane.
所以我就跑了出来
So I-I got outta there, and...
那是我最后一次见到她
That was the last time I saw her.
我不知道她会被杀死
I didn't know she would end up dead.
我想不到肖恩会杀了她
I didn't know Shane would kill her.
毫无疑问  像肖恩这种人肯定会杀了她
So no doubt a guy like Shane would kill her,
但是似乎又不是他杀的
but it's starting to look like he didn't.
他有不在场证明
He's got an alibi.
我不相信那证据
I don't believe it.
六个酒吧的老客户
Affidavits from six bar patrons,
在口供里都声称
all stating that Shane was there
在11点到12点之间肖恩在酒吧
between 11:00 and midnight.
其实他掌管着酒吧
Well, he practically runs the place,
他让那些人说什么他们就说什么
So the patrons will say what he tells 'em.
鉴证组刚刚确认了那辆车已完全被焚毁了
So C.S.U. just confirmed that his car
找不到跟纤维匹配的东西
was too burned for them to match the fibers
也无法取证
or pull forensics.
所以说我们甚至无法证明他那辆车运过尸体
So we can't even prove that he transported the vic's body.
我们也无法把凶器跟他扯上关系
We also can't tie the murder weapon to him either.
根据她的助理保罗所说
According to her assistant Paul,
霍莉通常携带一把点38口径的手枪自卫
Holly used to carry around a .380 pistol for protection.
她可能是被自己的枪所杀害的
She might have been killed with her own gun.
这说不通
Here's something that doesn't add up--
泰瑞斯·威尔顿的手机
Tyrese Wilton's phone.
为什么肖恩要让乔伊
Why would Shane tell Joey
去偷一部只值几百块钱的手机呢
to steal a phone worth a couple of hundred bucks?
况且是在一个有亮晃晃珠宝的派对上
Especially when there had to be so much bling at that party.
哥们  现在都不说"亮晃晃"了  那叫"闪瞎眼"
Dude, nobody says "bling" anymore. Try "shine."
还有件事说不通
There's something else that doesn't add up.
我们联系了所有的来宾
All the guests were contacted and asked
并询问他们是否丢失了什么个人物品
if they were missing any personal items.
他们都说没有  那么
They all said no, so--
为什么泰瑞斯·威尔顿没有说
Why didn't Tyrese Wilton mention
他的手机不见了呢
that his phone was gone?
看看这个  杨氏王朝
Check this out. "Yang Dynasty."
这可能是霍莉衣服上有花生油的原因
Could explain the peanut oil on Holly's clothes.
墙上有飞溅的血迹
There's blood spatter on the wall.
看来我们找到了犯罪现场
Looks like we found our crime scene.
是的  就在泰瑞斯的门口
Yep, and it's right at Tyrese's doorstep.
你是说霍莉是在我工作室的门口遇害的吗
Are you saying that Holly was killed just outside my studio?
没错
That's right.
你还是告诉我们她在干什么吧
So why don't you tell us what she was doing here?
我怎么知道
How the hell should I know?
那么  你就告诉我们
Mm. Well, then maybe you can tell us
派对那天的11点到12点之间
what you were doing between 11:00 and midnight
你在做什么吧
the night of the party.
我就在派对上
I was at the party.
我一直待到1点多
I stayed there till just after 1:00.
你可以去查
You can check.
你被询问过在那天晚上
You were also asked if any of your stuff went missing
是否丢过东西
the night of the party.
你没有提及你丢了的手机
You didn't mention your phone.
那是因为我的手机没丢
Because my phone wasn't missing.
你没必要跟我说谎  泰瑞斯
You don't have to lie to me, Tyrese.
我跟偷手机的那个孩子谈过了
I talked to the kid who stole it.
我是说  我的手机是不见了一两个小时
I mean, it was missing for an hour or two,
但是最后又出现了
but then it turned up.
看见了吗  派对结束时我在洗手间里找到的
See? I found it in the bathroom at the end of the night.
要是手机被乔伊偷了
If Joey stole the phone,
怎么会又出现在晚会上呢
how'd it end up back at the party?
把手机还回来的人不想让人发现它不见了
Whoever brought that back didn't want it missed.
根据肖恩的一贯手法
Based on Shane's M.O.,
他的目标是有价值的东西  能卖钱的东西
he was after something valuable, something he could sell.
泰瑞斯  你手机里有什么
Yo, Tyrese, what's on that phone--
财务信息  照片  有价值的资料之类的
Financial info, pictures, valuable data?
有样东西很重要
Only one thing that really matters--
这部手机还是一把电子钥匙
I use this phone as an e-key.
电子钥匙
An e-key?
可以进入工作室的电子钥匙
An electronic key. It opens up this studio.
霍莉知道这个吗
Well, did Holly know that?
是的  当我发现手机不见时我跟她说起过
Yeah, I mentioned it to her when I discovered it was gone.
我本来要用短信发给她我的号码
I went to text her my number,
但手机不见了  我只好写在她手上
But I had to write it on her hand instead.
这就是为什么霍莉来这的原因
That's why Holly was here.
她意识到肖恩偷这部手机
She realized that Shane stole the phone
是因为他要盗窃这件工作室
because he was gonna rip the studio off.
她想要阻止这件事
She couldn't let that happen,
因为泰瑞斯要用这里让她出名
not with Tyrese here about to give her big break.
对  所以她赶在你的东西被偷前
Right, so she races over here to confront Shane
来到这里跟肖恩对质
to stop him before he ripped you off.
看来她做到了  因为什么东西也没丢
Looks like she did, because nothing's missing.
你确定
You sure?
当然了  我这有价值两百多万的设备
Positive. I got over $2 mil in equipment here.
什么也
And nothing...
天啊
Oh, god.
-怎么了  -那些录音
- What?  - The recordings.
如果有人拿到了还没发行的专辑
If someone got their hands on an unreleased album...
那他就发达了
It'd be worth a fortune.
更不用说如果发布在网上  会严重影响销量
Not to mention tanking our record sales if it leaked online.
不  乔茜·朗的专辑文件
Oh, no. Josie Lang's album
在那天晚上的11点45被访问过
was accessed at 11:45 the night of the party.
有人下载过
Someone downloaded the masters.
肖恩干的
Shane.
我再说一遍  肖恩的不在场证据很充分
Look, I'm telling you, Shane's alibi is rock-solid.
这怎么可能
How is that even possible?
我们询问了酒吧里的每一个人
We interviewed everyone in the bar.
甚至还问了酒吧外的出租车司机
We even talked to the cabbies outside,
所有人都说他是在12点左右离开的
and everyone said that he left around midnight.
如果他没用他的车弃尸
Why would he torch his car
那他为什么要把它烧了呢
if he didn't use it to dump her body?
丢弃尸体的可能是他
He might have dumped the body,
但是时间线表明他不是凶手
But our timeline says that he did not kill her.
天啊
Man.
等  等一下  我们  我们
W-wait a minute. We--we--
我们一定是遗漏了什么
we gotta be missing something here.
让我们再梳理一遍
So let's just go over it again.
我们知道乔伊在11点左右把手机交给肖恩
We know that Joey handed Shane that phone around 11:00.
还知道乔茜的专辑是在11点45被下载的
And we know that Josie's album was downloaded at 11:45.
而霍莉是在11点到12点之间被杀的
Holly was murdered sometime between 11:00 and midnight.
等一下
Wait a minute.
整件事的关键就是那部手机
The key to this whole thing is that phone.
我们假设是肖恩
We're assuming that Shane
利用手机进入了工作室
was the one who used it to break in to the studio.
因为乔伊把手机交给了他
Because he's the one that Joey gave the phone to.
对  但是证人说11点半到12他都在酒吧里
Right, but witnesses place him at the bar, 11:30 to midnight.
而工作室里的专辑是在11点45被下载的
The album was downloaded at the studio at 11:45.
-这一定是另一个人干的  -谁呢
- It had to be someone else.  - Like who?
一定是晚会上的某个人
Well, it had to be someone from the party.
进入到工作室的这个人
So then whoever broke in to the studio
必须得把手机还回去
must have returned the phone to the party
这样泰瑞斯才不会发现手机被偷了
so that Tyrese wouldn't realize that it was even taken.
我们要做的就是找出
All we have to do is figure out
哪一位来宾能够通过
which one of the guests had something to gain
盗取乔茜的专辑获利
from stealing Josie's album.
一二  五六  七八
One, two. Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
一  二  三  四
Rock one, two, three, four.
伸脚  很好
Step. Nice. Good.
踮脚
Point again.
你们拿到我们
Did you guys not get
发过去的宾客名单了吗
the guest list that we sent over?
拿到了
Yeah, we... we did.
我们想要问问
We just need to ask you a few questions
派对当晚你的行程
about your schedule the night of the party.
好啊
Yeah, sure.
根据你的派对策划人所说
So according to your party planner,
你在11点消失了一段时间
you excused yourself at 11:00 to do a costume change
换衣服准备表演新专辑曲目
for a performance of a track from your new album.
是这样吗
Is that correct?
没错
That sounds about right,
但是他们让我去哪儿我就去哪儿
but I just go where they tell me to.
你们懂的
You know how it is.
不过策划人告诉我们你坚持
Only your planner told us that you insisted
准备一整个小时
on having a full hour.
你们试穿过紧身皮裤吗
Have you ever tried changing into skintight leather pants?
相当费时间
It's time-consuming.
为什么问这些
Why? What's-- what's the point?
这一小时给了你足够的时间
Well, that hour gave you enough time
前去泰瑞斯·威尔顿的工作室
to get to Tyrese Wilton's studio,
下载乔茜的新专辑
download Josie's new album,
再赶回派对表演歌曲
and get back to the party to perform your song.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
我干嘛要那么做
Why would I do anything like that?
因为这几年你的专辑销量下滑得厉害
Because your album sales have been sagging for years.
如果这张还是没能热卖
If your album didn't perform,
你的公司会与你解约
your record label was gonna drop you.
我跟和音360公司合作十年了
I've been with Harmony 360 for 10 years.
他们爱我
They love me.
乔茜·朗比你红不是什么秘密
It's no secret that Josie Lang's eclipsed you.
得了  她才出道几天啊
Oh, please. She's been around for two seconds.
一年后  没人会记得她的名字
Give it a year, you won't even remember her name.
那无所谓
It doesn't matter.
你们的专辑下周同时发行
Both your albums come out next week,
她的专辑卖得肯定比你好
and she's going to crush you.
除非有人在网上泄露乔茜的专辑
Unless someone mysteriously leaks josie's new album online.
你的计划很简单
Your plan was simple--
雇肖恩偷手机
Hire Shane to steal the phone,
那样你就能进入工作室
that way, you can get in to the studio.
你没想到的是霍莉出现了
The one thing that you didn't plan on was Holly.
她在你要离开工作室的时候
She showed up and caught you
把你抓了个正着
just as you were leaving the studio.
你怕她曝光你
You couldn't risk her exposing you.
你们扭打起来
You fought.
她掏出枪自卫
She pulled out her gun to protect herself,
但是你最终用那把枪杀了她
but you managed to use it on her instead.
于是你给肖恩打电话
So you called Shane
让他帮你处理尸体
and you got him to get rid of the body.
开什么玩笑  那都是猜测
Are you kidding me? That's all speculation.
有件事不是猜测  你雇了DJ比特
The one thing that's not speculation is that you hired D.J. Beat.
你是怎么知道她的
How'd you find out about her?
口口相传
Word of mouth.
别扯了  你的保镖跟肖恩是发小
More like your bodyguard grew up with Shane Winters.
肖恩让你雇霍莉
Shane had you hire d.J. Beat
这样乔伊就能进来偷手机了
So that Joey could get in and steal that phone.
还有一件事不是猜测
You know what else isn't speculation?
她在你网络提供商上使用的许可
The warrant she served on your I.S.P.
透露了一个邮件账号  是你创建的
that warrant revealed the e-mail account that you created
用来与泄露乔茜专辑的黑客联系
to communicate with the hacker that was going to leak josie's new album online.
这些证据够了吗
Is that enough fact for you?
我的专辑销量也许下滑了
My record sales may be down,
但我至少还是请得起好律师的
but I can still afford a damn good lawyer.
你总是出现
You keep showing up here like this,
我的手下会以为你喜欢我的
My boys are gonna think you're sweet on me.
不会了
Not anymore, they won't.
你现在可是窃盗重罪的嫌疑人
You are walking on grand larceny and accessory after the fact.
那种运气延续不了多长时间
Wow. Now that kind of luck does not last long.
看来今晚我得买彩票去了
Well, I guess I gotta go play the powerball, then, tonight.
这是我的枪
This is my gun.
这把是你的
And this one will be yours.
你要是再接近乔伊和其他孩子
You ever go near Joey or any other kid ever again,
事情会这样发生
The story's gonna go like this--
你袭击我
you pulled that piece on me.
然后
And...
我自卫
I had to defend myself, so...
杀了你
I killed you.
明白了吗
You understand me?
还是说你想演这出戏
Or should we play out that story
在这
right here,
现在
Right now?
我听见了
I hear you.
很好
Good.
拿后座的文件
Reach back there and grab that file.
我是你的秘书吗
What am I, your secretary?
拿就是了
Just grab the file.
我为了破案做得还不够吗
Look, haven't I done enough to solve this case for you?
看看
Read it.
哈维尔·埃斯波西托
"Juvenile record for
少年犯文档
Javier Esposito."
是的
Yep.
美好的时光
The good ol' days.
伤人  拒捕
So "Assault, resisting arrest"...
非法占有
Mm. "Unlawful possession."
是啊
Yeah.
你一团糟
You were a mess.
但我只知道干那些事
Yeah, but that's all I knew.
老爸死了  老妈干两份工作
Dad was gone, my mom was working two jobs.
在我们的街区  想要活下来
In my neighborhood, you had to do
什么事都得干
what you had to do to survive.
不是每个人都撑过来了
Not everybody made it.
你是不是要告诉我
Is this where you tell me that I need to
爷们一点  像你一样重新来过
man up and get my act together like you did?
不  不是那样的
No. It doesn't work like that.
你需要帮助
You need help.
对我来说  是我的一位老师
For me, it was one of my teachers.
在我身上看到了我都没看到的未来
Saw a future in me that I didn't even see in myself.
但最终是由我来做出选择
But it was up to me to make the choice,
走哪条路
to pick which road to go down.
我跟你的学校辅导员谈了
I talked to your school counselor.
-什么  -如果你逃学  她会告诉我
- What? - She's gonna call me if you keep ditching.
拜托  老兄
Come on, man.
我每周会给你打电话
And I'm gonna call you once a week,
打探你的情况
check in.
好吧  我去上学
All right, I'll go...
但你要保证换家具
If you agree to get new furniture.
有那个破家具
You can't get laid on the regular
你没法性福
with that junk you have.
我是为了你好
I'm just looking out for you.
给你
Here.
有事的话
If you need anything,
不管什么时候
day or night,
打这个电话
you call me at that number.
好
Okay.
你还好啦
You're all right...
对于条子来说
For a cop.
我知道
I know.
滚出我的车
Now get out of my car.